# **Muhammad Rizki**

Bandung, Indonesia | 0831-6491-9535 | <a href="mailto:mrizki135790@gmail.com">mrizki135790@gmail.com</a> | LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rizki-muhammad-32b4b4203/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/rizki-muhammad-32b4b4203/</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://portfolio-rizki.vercel.app/">https://portfolio-rizki.vercel.app/</a>

#### **PROFILE**

Certified Google Associate Cloud Engineer with experience in cloud computing, data science, and software development. Skilled in designing, implementing, and optimizing systems, with a passion for learning new technologies. Strong collaborator who excels in a team environment and is effective at problem-solving.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# $Universitas\ Pendidikan\ Indonesia-Bandung, Indonesia$

Sep 2023 – Jun 2024

Teaching Assistant

- Led practicum sessions for 80+ students in Visual Mobile Programming, Data Warehouse, and Data Mining, enhancing their hands-on skills.
- Developed and delivered learning modules on Dart, Flutter, FastAPI, and data science concepts in Python, including machine learning and deep learning
- Strengthened student expertise in version control with Git and GitHub, preparing them for collaborative software development.

# PT. Sineas Kreatif Indonesia – Bandung, Indonesia

*Mar* 2024 – *May* 2024

Back End Developer

- Developed and maintained back-office applications using Laravel, streamlining company operations in a film media production and creative agency environment.
- Collaborated closely with the front-end team to manage data requirements and ensure seamless integration

# PT. Sinergi Inovasi Tekno – Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2024 – Mar 2024

Flutter Developer

- Developed 2 mobile apps by translating UI designs into Flutter code.
- Utilized GetX for state and route management, contributing to a 20% improvement in application performance.

# **EDUCATION**

Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia — Bandung, Indonesia S1 — Computer Science (GPA: 3.89/4.00)	Sep 2021 – present
Digital Talent – Bandung, Indonesia Junior Web Developer	Jul 2024 – Aug 2024
Bangkit Academy – Bandung, Indonesia Cloud Computing (Score: 92/100)	Aug 2023 – Jan 2024
Rakamin Academy X IDX Partners – Bandung, Indonesia Data Scientist (Score: 81/100)	Oct 2023 – Nov 2023

# SELECTED PROJECTS

**DSS Website** (2024) Web application that assists in decision making using the Weighted Product

method to evaluate alternatives based on several criteria that have their

respective weights.

Minatku (2024) As a Backend developer and Cloud Engineer on the career and college

preparation application project "MinatKu". This application can provide

appropriate career path suggestions for users using AI.

LenderUp (2023) As a Flutter developer and backend developer on a peer-to-peer (P2P) lending

mobile application project that connects borrowers and lenders to conduct

transactions. This application focuses on funding MSMEs to advance the middle

to lower economy.

School Profile Developed a school profile website for SMA 13 Bandung, West Java using the

Website (2023) php framework, Laravel.

# **ORGANIZATION**

**Hellocation ID & Hellocation Korean**– *IT Manager* **Google Developer Student Club** – *Member* 

Jun 2024 – Present Dec 2022 – Jan 2024

# **OTHERS**

**Technical-skills** Node.js, React, Next.Js, Bootstrap, Laravel, Node.js, Flutter, Figma, Git & Github,

HTML & CSS, Scikit-learn, Tensorflow, FastAPI, Flask, docker, Google Cloud

Platform, SOL.

**Certifications** Asociate Cloud Enginer, Alibaba Cloud Developer, The British Institute